<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recapped</string>
    <string name="firstimage">image</string>
    <string name="author">Kelvin Joshua</string>
    <string name="hint">Enter Hobbies</string>
    <string name="buttonText">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="placeholder">According to statistics, about me pages are among the ten most visited by potential customers on your site.
The “about us” page is a must-have page (this can be a page on your website, separate landing page or even “about me” website as a type of portfolio) used by all types of businesses to give customers more insight into who is involved with a given business and exactly what it does.
Your “About me” page forms the first impression of a company or product, puts a name and a face to your business, and gives website visitor the opportunity to develop a connection with you (a good reason for a visitor to stay on your website!), and it is your best chance to convert more visits to enquiries/more enquiries to customers.
About me page is a space for individuality and originality, it is an important marketing tool that should convince. Therefore, they are very different!
Let’s get the best of the top About us samples and learn how to write about me page, that will pull your customers like a magnet.
        This site is a great example of what we have said before: sometimes it’s enough to create an excellent “About me” page to promote your brand (which, actually, will work as a full-fledged website).
We like the sleek design and beautiful photos that complement it. You find it fascinating too? Here is proof that simple sites work efficiently! “All the great things are simple”, right?
As you can see, the simple and intuitive Weblium editor helps anyone create an attractive website in the shortest possible time, without having special knowledge of web development. Simplicity is the new ingenuity!
This is a good example of an attractive minimalistic portfolio of a creative person, where the “About me” information is perfectly integrated into the design of the website.
An elegant trendy dark background with geometric patterns, simple and clear navigation – this is what a modern portfolio should look like!
Since all Weblium templates are developed on the basis of a deep study of the niche and harmoniously combine the most current trends in web design, sometimes it’s enough to simply choose a template, add your own unique content and get a beautiful website with the perfect navigation for your type of business!This example of the classic “About us” page with extremely comfortable navigation and vibrant colors is quite impressive, isn’t it?
You already want to buy a lizard and make it your pet? Then choose the Weblium template that you like the most, create your own website for business – and wait for your new customers to come!
</string>
</resources>